风暴就要来了 而你们两个 你们就摇逸在风暴的中心
Storm's coming and you boys, you are smack in the middle of it.
爸爸想让我们继承他的事业 救助他人 猎杀魔鬼
Dad wants us to pick up where he left off. Saving people, hunting things.
- 家族事业 - 我希望尽我们所能去拯救更多的人
- The family business. - We gotta save as many people as we can.
迪恩 你和我都看到过… 大多数人想象不到的魔鬼
Dean, you and I have seen things most people couldn't even dream about.
如果这是超自然的东西 我们就杀了它们 这就是我们的工作
If it's supernatural we kill it. That's our job.
不 迪恩 这不是我们的工作 我们要做的是猎杀恶魔
No, Dean, that is not our job. Our job is hunting evil.
他们都一样 萨姆 他们不是人类 懂吗？
Well, they're all the same, Sam. They're not human, okay?
我们必须把他们每一个都杀光
We have to exterminate them.
我们的生活就是怪诞奇异的 兄弟
Our lives are weird, man.
这还用你说吗
You're telling me.
- 我们迷路了 - 不 这是条捷径
- We're lost. - No, this is a shortcut.
亲爱的 只是我们在这条路上 已经开了一个多小时了
Babe, it's just we've been on this road over an hour.
而我们连一辆车的影子都没看到
We haven't seen a single car.
莫莉 我懂怎么看这该死的地图 好吗？
Molly, I know how to read a frigging map, okay?
之前我们路过了一个加油站 还是找个人问下
We passed that gas station. Let's just go ask someone.
那是40分钟之前的事了 我们可不要再转回去
That was 40 minutes ago. We're not turning around.
算了吧 这样的争论是不是有点老土了？
Come on. Isn't this argument a little archaic?
- 现在的时代男人是可以问路的 - 哦 不 不能 我们不能
- Men can ask directions these days. - Oh, no, no, we can't.
这和我的基因相反 你瞧 我知道我们具体在哪儿
It's against our genetic code. Look, I know exactly where we are.
哦 是吗？在哪？
Oh, yeah, where?
99号公路 好吗？直接就能穿过去
Highway 99, okay? It cuts right through.
99号公路？
Highway 99?
好吧 我们走的是观光路线
Okay, so we're taking the scenic route.
大卫
David.
今天是我们的周年纪念 我们却不得不呆在这车里度过
It's our anniversary and we're spending it stuck in the car.
我知道 我很抱歉
I know. I'm sorry.
让我补偿你一下 好吗？来吧
Hey, let me make it up to you, okay? Come here.
住手 我生你气了
No. Stop. I'm mad at you.
算了吧 莫莉
Oh, come on, Molly.
你爱我的
Hey, you love me.
不 我不爱 你是个混蛋
No, I don't. You're a jerk.
- 大卫 我是说真的 - 莫莉
- David, I mean it. - Ha, ha-Molly!
大卫？
David?
大
Da?
大卫？
David?
大
Da?
大卫？
David?
你好？
Hello?
有人在吗？
Is anyone here?
你好
Hello?
是你
It's you.
你没事 我真的很抱歉 我没看到你在哪儿
You're okay. I'm so sorry. I didn't see you there.
你… 你受伤了？
Are you? Are you hurt?
先生
Sir?
[邪恶力量 第2季第16集]
停车
Stop!
天啊
Holy!
你们得帮帮我
You've gotta help me.
求你了 求你了
Please, please.
好好好 冷静点 冷静点 告诉我们发生什么事了？
All right, all right, calm down. Calm down. Tell us what happened.
我突然转向 然后发生了车祸 当我清醒过来
I swerved and we crashed. And when I came to…
车已经报废了 我的丈夫也不见了
uh, the car was wrecked. My husband was missing.
我四处寻找他 不过那个在公路上的男人
I went looking for him but that's when the man from the road…
他… 他开始追我
he started chasing me.
他的头发和胡须是不是看起来像割草机修过一样？
Did he look like he lost a fight with a lawnmower?
你怎么知道？
How did you know that?
碰大运而已
Lucky guess.
女士 你叫什么名字？
Madam, what's your name?
莫莉 莫莉·麦克纳摩拉
Molly. Molly McNamara.
我想也许你应该跟我们一起走 我们把你送到镇上
Maybe you should come with us. We'll take you back into town-
我不能 我要去找大卫 他可能已经回车里了
I can't. I have to find David. He might've gone back to the car.
我们首先得把你送到一个安全的地方 然后迪恩和我会回来
We should get you somewhere safe. Dean and I will come back here.
- 找你的丈夫的 - 不 我不能丢下他一个人离开这里
- We'll look for your husband. - No. I'm not leaving here without him.
可以陪我回我车那里吗 求你了？
Would you just take me back to my car, please?
当然 来吧
Of course. Come on.
就在那边
It's right over there.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我确定车就是在这儿 我… 我们撞到那棵树 就在那里
I'm sure this is where it was. We hit that tree right there.
这… 这没有道理啊
This doesn't make any sense.
迪恩 我们得离开这里 葛瑞利可能在任何时候出现
We gotta get out of here. Greeley could show up at any second.
- 你要怎么告诉她？- 真相
- What're you gonna tell her? - The truth.
她会吓的朝另外一个方向跑的
She's gonna take off running in the other direction.
我知道这听起来有点疯狂 不过我的确是撞到那棵树了
I know it sounds crazy, but I crashed into that tree.
我不知道谁能把车搬走了 车已经撞报废了
I don't know who could've taken it. It was totaled.
求求你们了 你们得相信我
Please, you have to believe me.
莫莉 听着 我们的确相信你 这就是为什么我们得带你离开这里
Listen, we do believe you, all right? That's why we wanna get you out of here.
大卫怎么办？肯定有什么事发生了 我得去报警
But what about David? Something must have happened. I have to get to the cops.
报警 这是个很棒的主意 我们会亲自把你送到警察局 好吗？
Cops. That's a great idea. We'll take you down to the station ourselves.
就… 就跟我们走吧 这是我们能帮你和你丈夫的最好方法
So just come with us. It's the best way we can help you and your husband.
好吧
Okay.
我们现在本应该是到了太浩湖的
We're supposed to be in Lake Tahoe.
你和大卫？
You and David?
- 今天是我们5周年结婚纪念 - 糟透了的周年纪念
- It's our five-year anniversary. - A hell of an anniversary.
就在刚刚之前 我们在冷战
Right before, we were having the dumbest fight.
这是仅有的一次真正的争吵 当我们困在车里的时候
It's the only time we ever argue, when we're stuck in the car.
我知道发生什么了
Yeah, I know how that goes.
你知道我最后对他说的话吗？
You know the last thing I said to him?
我说他是个混蛋
I called him a jerk.
哦 天哪…
Oh, God.
如果这… 如果这成为我对他所说的最后一句话
What if that's the last thing I said to him?
莫莉
Molly.
我们会弄清楚你丈夫到底发生了什么事 我向你保证
We're gonna figure out what happened to your husband. I promise.
- 是你？- 不是
- Did you? - No.
我担心过你这样回答
Great. I was afraid you'd say that.
这歌
This song…
- 怎么？- 发生车祸的时候也在播这歌
- What? - It was playing when we crashed.
她是我的
She's mine.
她是我的 她是我的
She's mine. She's mine.
那是什么
What is that?
坐稳
Hold on.
你要干什么
What are you doing?
刚刚…
What the…?
- 刚刚到底发生了什么事？- 别担心 莫莉 一切都会没事的
- What the hell just happened? - Don't worry, Molly. Everything's all right.
话说的有点太早了 萨姆
I think you spoke a little too soon, Sammy.
我想他是不会让她离开的
I don't think he's gonna let her leave.
这种事是不可能发生的
This can't be happening.
呃…
Well…
相信我 的确发生了
trust me, it's happening.
好了 谢谢你们的帮助 我想从这里开始我自己就可以了
Well, okay, thanks for helping, but I think I got it covered from here.
- 等等 莫莉 莫莉 等一下 - 别跟着我
- Wait, Molly, wait a minute. - Just leave me alone.
- 不 求你了 你得听我说 - 别过来
- No. You have to listen to me. - Just stay away.
我们碰上你并不是一个巧合 好吗？
It wasn't a coincidence that we found you, all right?
你在说什么？
What're you talking about?
当我们刚刚碰上你的时候… 我们并不是在载着美眉兜风… 姐妹儿
We weren't cruising for chicks when we ran into you.
我们本来就是跑到这里来猎捕的
We were already out here. Hunting.
猎捕什么？
Hunting for what?
鬼
Ghosts.
- 别… 应该委婉的告诉她 - 你们是疯子
- Don't sugarcoat it for her. - You're nuts.
真的吗？就和那个内脏像粉一样 灰飞烟灭的家伙一样疯吗？
Really? About as nuts as a vanishing guy with his guts spilling out.
你清楚你看到了什么
You know what you saw.
我们认为他的名字叫约拿格雷利
We think his name is Jonah Greeley.
他是15年前死在这条路上的当地农民
He was a local farmer that died 15 years ago on this highway.
别… 说了
Just stop.
每一年 在他死忌的晚上…
One night a year, on the anniversary of his death…
他会在这条路上出现
he haunts this road.
这就是我们在这里的原因 莫莉
That's why we're here, Molly…
要试着阻止他
to try and stop him.
现在 我猜也是这只鬼把我的车弄消失的了
Yeah, I suppose this ghost made my car disappear too.
疯狂的事情发生了 对吧？
Crazier things have happened, huh?
你知道吗？我都已经快疯掉了 我要自己去报警
You know what? I'm all filled up on crazy. I'm gonna get the cops myself.
我不想把话说的太直 但是我想你不会跑出去太远的
I don't mean to be harsh, but I don't think you're gonna get too far.
这是什么意思？
What's that supposed to mean?
意思是说原本计划就是带你离开
It means that plan A was trying to get you out of here.
很显然计划因为… 农民公路杀手而进行的不太顺利
Obviously, that didn't go over too well with, uh, Farmer Roadkill.
莫莉 我们说的是事实
Molly, we're telling the truth.
格雷利是不会让你离开这条公路的
Greeley's not gonna let you leave this highway.
你是…
You're…?
你是认真的 对吗？
You're serious about this, aren't you?
毫无疑问
Deadly.
每年
Every year,
格雷利都要找某人… 为了曾经发生在他身上的事情而进行惩罚
Greeley finds someone to punish for what happened to him.
今晚那个人就是你
Tonight, that person is you.
为什么是我？我什么都没有做
Why me? I didn't do anything.
和这没有关系
It doesn't matter.
在某些鬼魂眼中 他们只能看到他们想要的东西
Some spirits only see what they want.
那么你们说的这个格雷利 他带走了我的丈夫？
So you're saying this Greeley, he took my husband?
哦 上帝啊
Oh, God.
莫莉 你瞧 我们会帮忙的 好吗？
Molly, look, we're gonna help, all right?
但首先 你要帮助我们
But first, you gotta help us.
帮助你们？
Help you?
怎么帮？
How?
就是这里 这就是我看到他的地方
This is it. This is where I saw him.
一定是他的猎捕小屋了
Must've been his hunting cabin.
看起来真是个讨人喜欢的家伙
Seemed like a real sweet guy.
- 外面没有墓碑或者墓石 - 你在找格雷利的坟墓？
- No markers or headstones outside. - You're looking for Greeley's grave?
- 是的 - 为什么？
- Yeah. - Why?
这样我们就可以把他的尸体挖出来 撒上盐并且烧掉他
So we can dig up the corpse and salt and burn it.
哦 当然了 本来就该这样
Oh, sure. Naturally.
这是除掉鬼魂的方法
It's a way to get rid of a spirit.
那样会救大卫？
And that'll save David?
这就是可以帮助你们二人的方法 如果可以找到尸体的话
Well, this is what'll help both of you. Provided there's a corpse to be found.
那么我们如何才能找到尸体？
So how do we find it?
呃 说不好 格雷利死后 他的妻子领回了尸体
I'm not sure. After Greeley died, his wife claimed the body.
那就是其他人最后一次看见她
That's the last anyone saw of her.
所以好的可能性是她把他带回到这里了
Good guess she brought him back here…
但是他们有几千英亩的地 他可能被埋在任何地方
but they had a thousand acres. He could be buried anywhere on them.
你们就是干这个的？你们就像是捉鬼赶死队
So this is really what you guys do. You're like Ghostbusters.
是的 除了他们那套制服以外 这真的是场很投机的谈话
Yeah, minus the jumpsuits. Look, this is a fascinating conversation and all…
但是这条公路每年只闹一次鬼
but this highway's only haunted once a year.
我们在日出之前把他搞定 你说怎么样
We got till sunup to wrap this thing up.
我们继续 好吗？太好了
What do you say we move it along? Great.
- 我们在找什么？- 格雷利的房子
- What are we looking for? - Greeley's house.
也许他被埋在那里 找一条路或者小道什么的 跟紧点
Maybe he's buried there. Look for roads or paths or something. Stay close.
恩 好的
Yeah. Okay.
莫莉
Molly.
莫莉 帮帮我 莫莉
Help me. Molly.
大卫？
David?
大卫？大卫
David? David?
哎哟
Whoops.
嘿 你还好吗？
Hey, are you all right?
那个婊子养的到底对我丈夫做了什么？
What has that son of a bitch done with my husband?
放松点 好吗？你会再见到大卫的
Just take it easy, all right? You're gonna see David again.
- 你会的 - 嘿
- You will. - Hey.
沿着阴森的砖头路走
Follow the creepy brick road.
走吧
Go ahead.
那东西是射击盐块的？
That thing shoots rock salt?
是的
Yep.
用盐可以防范鬼魂？
And plain salt keeps away spirits?
简单的总是最好的
Simple remedies are always the best.
在大多数文化中 盐象征纯洁 所以可以抵御邪恶和肮脏的东西
Most cultures, saIt's a symbol of purity so it repels impure and unnatural things.
这就和你把他们从肩膀上扔出去是一个道理
Same reason you throw it over your shoulder.
知道吗 只有这次 我喜欢眼前突然… 看见一座漂亮的房子
You know, just once I'd like to round the corner and see a nice house.
外面有墓碑吗？是的 没错 有过这么容易的事吗？
Any headstones outside? Yeah, right. Is it ever that easy?
我猜没有
I guess not.
你们两个检查楼上
You two check upstairs.
看能不能找到什么笔记或者记录…
See if you can find notes or records where he's buried.
- 我检查楼下 - 好吧
- I'll just check down here. - All right.
太棒了
Great.
看看这个
Look at this.
这是格雷利和他的妻子
It's Greeley and his wife.
这是他给她写的一封情书
It's a love letter he wrote her.
我的上帝啊 这写的太美了
My God, it's beautiful.
我不明白这样的一个人… 是如何变成那样的怪物的
I don't understand how a guy like this can turn into that monster.
像格雷利这样的鬼魂像是 呃…
spirits like Greeley are, uh…
像是受伤的动物
like wounded animals.
迷失了
Lost.
承受经历了太多的痛苦
In so much pain that they lash out.
为什么？为什么他们在这儿？
Why? Why are they here?
他们的一些… 把他们留在了这里…
Well, there's some part of them that's keeping them here.
就像他们残留的 呃…
Like their remains, or, um…
未完成的事
unfinished business.
未完成的事？
"Unfinished business"?
是的
Yeah, uh…
可能是复仇 可能是爱情 或者是憎恨
It could be revenge. It could be love or hate.
无论是什么原因 都把他们缠的太紧了
Whatever it is, they just hold on too tight.
放不开
Can't let go.
所以他们就被套牢了
So they're trapped.
如此的循环下去
Caught in the same loops.
不断的重复着惨剧 反反复复
Replaying the same tragedies over and over.
听起来你为他们感到遗憾
You sound almost sorry for them.
他们不是邪恶的人 知道吗？
Well, they weren't evil people. You know, the
他们中的许多都曾是很好的人 只不过…
A lot of them were good. Just…
一些事情发生在他们身上
Something happened to them.
一些他们无法控制的事情
Something they couldn't control.
当像这样的事情发生的时候… 萨姆也像珍妮弗洛夫休伊特一样
Sammy's getting a little J. Love Hewitt when it comes to things like this.
我 跟他们不一样 我绝对不会为他们做任何道歉的
Me, I don't like them and I sure as hell aingt making apologies for them.
楼下没什么东西 你们找到什么了吗？
There's nothing downstairs. You find anything?
只是他们曾经所有的信或者是字条
Uh, just about every piece of mail or receipt they ever had.
看到了一对夫妻的过去 但是目前还没有关于墓地的东西
Looked through a couple, but nothing about a grave so far.
- 什么？- 这后面有什么东西
- What? - There's something behind here.
拿着
Here.
从里面锁上了
It's locked from the inside.
闻起来像是有个老女人在这里
It smells like old lady in here.
这就解释清楚为什么了
And that would explain why.
现在我们知道为什么 没有人再次见到她了
Well, now we know why nobody ever saw her again.
她不想失去他后继续活下去了
She didn't wanna live without him.
迪恩 来帮把手
Dean, give me a hand.
真的吗？
Really?
你们要做什么？
What are you gonna do?
- 我们不能就这样留下她 - 为什么不？
- We can't leave her like this. - Why not?
她应该得到安息 迪恩
She deserves to be put to rest, Dean.
那么…
Son of a…
那么 如果你们也让格雷利得到安息的话…
So if you manage to put Greeley to rest too…
他们会怎么样？
what happens to him?
女士 这样的答案可远超出我们的工资等级了
Lady, that answer is way beyond our pay grade.
你们猎捕这些东西 但是你却不知道他们会怎么样？
You hunt these things but you don't know what happens to them?
他们永远不会再回来了 这才是重要的
They never come back. That's all that matters.
在他们放下了无论是什么 束缚他们留下的东西 他们…
After they let go of whatever is keeping them here…
他们就离开了
they just go.
我希望是某处更好的地方 但是我们不知道
I hope someplace better, but we don't know.
没人知道
No one does.
那么你们烧掉他们的尸骨后会怎么样？
What happens when you burn their bones?
呃…
Um…
我爸爸曾经说… 对于灵魂那就像是死亡的意思 你明白吗？
Well, my dad used to say that it was like death for ghosts, you know?
但是… 事实是 我们还是不知道 不确定
But the truth is, we still don't know, not for sure.
我猜这就是为什么我们 都如此的渴望生命的继续
I guess that's why we all hold onto life so hard…
即使是死去的
even the dead.
我们都只是害怕未知的事物
We're all just scared of the unknown.
我唯一害怕的事情就是失去大卫
The only thing I'm scared of is losing David.
我一定要再次见到他
I have to see him again.
我一定要
I have to.
- 我想我们应该告诉关于他丈夫的事情 - 我们不能
- We should tell her about her husband. - We can't.
迪恩 让她为了他而悲伤憔悴 这是很残忍的
Dean, it's cruel, letting her pine for him like this.
- 我不想让她蒙在鼓里 - 这是为了她好
- I don't like keeping her in the dark. - It's for her own good.
伙计 我知道你很内疚 但我们得按计划行事
I know you feel guilty, but let's just stick to the plan.
- 我们先把她带出去 然后再告诉她 - 告诉我什么？
- Let's get her out of here, then we'll tell. - Tell me what?
你们有什么事没告诉我？
What aren't you telling me?
一定是关于大卫的 你们知道他发生了什么
It's about David. You know what happened to him.
- 莫莉… - 萨姆 别…
- Molly. - Sam, don't.
别什么？
Don't what?
不告诉我因为我会 打乱了你们的猎捕计划？
Don't tell me because I'll mess up your hunt?
- 你们不关心我或者我的丈夫 - 这不是真的
- You don't care about me or my husband. - That's not true.
是吗？
Really?
那么无论是什么 告诉我 求你们了
Then whatever it is, tell me, please.
他来了
He's coming.
待在她身边
Stay with her.
她是我的
She's mine.
迪恩 他抓走了莫莉
Dean! He's got Molly.
这家伙真固执
This guy is persistent.
- 我们必须找到莫莉 - 我们要找到格雷利的尸骨
- We gotta find Molly. - We gotta find Greeley's bones.
而且 呃… 不要有压力或者其他的什么
And, uh, no pressure or anything…
但日出离我们只有不到2小时了
but we got less than two hours before sunrise.
嘿
Hey.
你找到什么了？
What do you got?
1992年2月6号 这是好象是事故发生前的两个星期 对吧？
Uh, "February 6, 1992." That was like two weeks before the accident, wasn't it?
是的 这看上去像是狩猎的小屋
Yeah. I mean, it looks like the hunting cabin…
但是… 我确信就在他们站的位置旁边 应该有一棵树才对
but I swear there's a tree there right where they're standing.
- 早应该想到了 - 什么？
- I should've thought of it. - What?
这是个古老的乡村习俗 迪恩 种一棵树来做为坟墓的标记
It's an old country custom, Dean. Planting a tree as a grave marker.
你真像是本活的怪诞百科全书
You're like a walking encyclopedia of weirdness.
是 我知道
Yeah, I know.
大卫在哪儿？你对他做了什么？
Where's David? What did you do to him?
你不应该再为他担心什么了
You shouldn't worry about him anymore.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
你该为自己担心一下了
You should worry about yourself.
- 我从来没有对你做过任何事 - 哦？
- I didn't do anything to you. - Oh.
我… 我知道你妻子的事 伤害我也换不回她的
No. I know about your wife. Hurting me won't bring her back.
我的妻子已经死了
My wife is gone.
所有留给我所要做的事就是伤害你
All I got left's hurting you.
求… 求求你了 就放我走吧
Please. Please, just let me go.
放你走？
Go?
你走不了的
You're not gonna leave.
你永远都走不了的
You're never gonna leave.
去救莫莉
Go get Molly.
感谢上帝
Oh, thank God.
叫我迪恩
Yeah, call me Dean.
这家伙真的把我惹恼了
This guy's really pissing me off.
快点 萨姆
Hurry up, Sam!
哦 亲爱的 今晚可真难熬啊
Oh, baby, it's been a long night.
好了
All right…
让我们带你离开这里吧
let's get you out of here.
除非你们告诉我 我的丈夫到底发生了什么… 否则我是不会走的
I'm not going anywhere until you tell me what happened to my husband.
- 莫莉… - 一直以来
- Molly. - All this time…
你知道我一直都在找他
I've been looking for him and you knew that…
你们知道的… 你们知道格雷利杀了他 不是吗？
You knew that Greeley killed him, didn't you?
他死了
He's dead.
不 莫莉
No, Molly.
大卫还活着
David's alive.
什么？
What?
你确定吗？
You're sure?
我很确定
I'm sure.
我们带你去见他 上车吧
We'll take you to him. Come on.
他就在那边的房子里
He's in that house, right there.
我不明白
I don't understand.
你会的
You will.
那…
That's not…
这不可能
It can't be.
发生了什么事？
What's happening?
那是谁？
Who is that?
那是大卫的妻子
That's David's wife.
我很抱歉 莫莉
I'm sorry, Molly.
15年前 你和你丈夫开车撞死了格雷利
Fifteen years ago, you and your husband hit Jonah Greeley with your car.
大卫幸存了下来
David survived.
你在说什么？
What are you saying?
41号公路不止一个灵魂
We're saying that there isn't just one spirit haunting Highway 41.
那有两个
There are two.
格雷利和你
Jonah Greeley and you.
在这15年间 一年中有一个晚上 你会出现在公路上
For the past 15 years, one night a year you've been appearing on that highway.
不 这不可能
No, that's not possible.
那是我们的结婚纪念日… 2月22号…
It was our anniversary, February 22nd…
- 1992年 - 是的
- 1992. - Yes.
莫莉 现在已经是2007年了
Molly, it's 2007.
上帝啊
Oh, God.
- 跟我说说41好公路 - 15年来有12起事故
- All right, tell me about Highway 41. - Twelve accidents over 15 years.
5起致命 全部都发生在同一个晚上
Five of them fatal. All of them happening on the same night.
我们要找的是什么… 州际死亡区？搭车鬼灵？
What are we looking at? Interstate dead zone? Phantom hitchhiker?
不完全是
Not quite.
我是说 一年接一年 目击者都陈述说是同一种东西令他们发生车祸
I mean, year after year, witnesses said the same thing made them crash:
一个女人出现在路中间
A woman appearing in the middle of the road…
后面是一个满身是血的男人
being chased by a man covered in blood.
两个幽灵？
Two spooks?
莫莉葬在哪儿了？
Now, where is Molly buried?
她… 她没被下葬
She…She wasn't buried anywhere.
她被火化了
She was cremated.
- 焚化尸骨的事就到此为止了 - 那是什么让她一直出现的？
- So much for burning her bones. - Yeah, but then what's keeping her here?
莫莉
Molly! Ahh!
有些幽灵只能看到他们想要的东西
Some spirits only see what they want.
大卫？
David?
停车 停车
Stop! Stop!
天啊
Holy!
你们得帮帮我
You have to help me.
迪恩 我想她不知道自己已经死了
Dean, I don't think she knows she's dead.
求求你了 请开门 求求你了
Please. Open up, please?
好了 好了 冷静下来 告诉我们到底发生了什么事？
Okay. All right, just calm down. Tell us what happened.
- 你要告诉她什么？- 真相
- What are you gonna tell her? - The truth.
她会被吓的朝另外的方向跑的
She's gonna take off running in the other direction.
有些幽灵被束缚的太紧
Some spirits hold on too tight.
放不开
Can't let go.
那格雷利呢？
And Greeley?
每年他都要为他的死而惩罚某人
Each year he punishes somebody for his death.
追赶他们
Uh, chasing them…
折磨他们
torturing them.
每一年
And each year…
那个某人就是你
that somebody is you.
可我一点也不记得了
But I don't remember any of it.
因为你看不到真相 莫莉
Because you couldn't see the truth, Molly.
这就是他不
So that's why he won't…
让我离开那条公路的原因
let me off the highway.
因为我…
Because I…
我撞死了他
I killed him.
我杀死了他们两个人
I killed us both.
你们第一次见到我的时候 为什么不告诉我？
Why didn't you tell me when you first saw me?
- 为什么要等到现在？- 你不会相信我们的
- Why wait until now? - You wouldn't have believed us.
你们把我当做诱饵
And you needed me for bait.
我们需要你
Well, we needed you.
大卫
David.
莫莉 我们带你来这里 是想让你能向前走
Molly, we brought you here so you could move on.
不 我得告诉他
No, I have to tell him.
告诉他什么？
Tell him what?
你爱他？你很抱歉？
That you love him? That you're sorry?
莫莉 这些他都知道
Molly, he already knows that.
如果你想进去 我们是不会阻止你的
If you wanna go in there, we're not gonna stop you.
但你会把他吓坏的
Yeah, but you are gonna freak him right out…
一辈子
for life.
大卫已经和你告过别了 莫莉 现在轮到你了
David's already said his goodbyes, Molly. Now it's your turn.
这是你未完成的事
This is your unfinished business.
我到底该怎么做？
What am I supposed to do?
就…
Just…
放手吧
let go…
为了大卫 为了一切
of David, of everything.
如果你能这样做…
You do that…
我们认为你就能向前走了
we think you'll move on.
但你们不知道我会去哪儿
But you don't know where.
不知道
No.
莫莉 你不属于这里
Molly, you don't belong here.
你还没受够折磨吗？
Haven't you suffered long enough?
是时候了
It's time.
是时候离开了
It's time to go.
看来她并不是个太坏的… 鬼魂
I guess she wasn't so bad for a ghost.
你认为她真的会去一个更好的地方吗？
You think she's really going to a better place?
我希望是这样
I hope so.
我们猜我们永远都不会知道的 直到我们亲身体验过后
I guess we'll never know. Not until we take the plunge ourselves, huh?
这都不重要 迪恩
Doesn't really matter, Dean.
抱有希望才是关键
Hope is kind of the whole point.
好了 海利乔
All right, Haley Joel.
我们上路吧
Let's hit the road.